(soft pop music)
♪ Hmm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Please try to forgive me ♪
♪ Stay here, don't put out the glow ♪
♪ Hold me now, don't bother ♪
♪ If every minute it makes me weaker ♪
♪ You can save me ♪
♪ From the man that I've become ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Looking back on the things I've done ♪
♪ I was trying to be someone ♪
♪ I played my part ♪
♪ Kept you in the dark ♪
♪ Now let me show you ♪
♪ The shape of my heart ♪
♪ Sadness is beautiful ♪
♪ Loneliness is tragical ♪
♪ So help me ♪
♪ I can't win this war ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ Touch me now, don't bother ♪
♪ If every second it makes me weaker ♪
♪ You can save me ♪
♪ From the man I've become ♪
♪ Looking back on the things I've done ♪
♪ Back on the things I've done ♪
♪ I was trying to be someone ♪
♪ Trying ♪
♪ I played my part ♪
♪ Kept you in the dark ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ Now let me show you
the shape of my heart ♪
♪ I'm here with my confession ♪
♪ Got nothing to hide no more ♪
♪ I don't know where to start ♪
♪ But to show you ♪
♪ The shape of my heart ♪
♪ I'm looking back on things I've done ♪
♪ I never wanna play the same old part ♪
♪ I'll keep you in the dark ♪
♪ Keep you in the dark ♪
♪ Now let me show you
the shape of my heart ♪
♪ Looking back on the things I've done ♪
♪ I was trying to be someone ♪
♪ Trying to be someone ♪
♪ I played my part ♪
♪ Kept you in the dark ♪
♪ Now let me show you ♪
♪ The shape of my heart ♪
♪ The true shape of my heart ♪
♪ Looking back on the things I've done ♪
♪ I was trying to be someone ♪
♪ I played my part ♪
♪ Kept you in the dark ♪
♪ Now let me show you the shape of ♪
♪ Show you the shape ♪
♪ Of my heart ♪